https://www.seerpharma.com/privacy-policy

Click here to read the SeerPharma (UK) Privacy Notice
SeerPharma is bound by the National Privacy Principles (NPPs) set out in the Federal Privacy Act 1988. This privacy policy outlines how we collect your personal information and what steps we take to protect that information. By accessing the website, you are agreeing to this privacy policy.
Collection of your personal information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you such as when you register for a training course or fill in a form on our website. The personal information that we collect may include your name, e-mail address, company name, phone number and company address.
The information provided in the online registration form enables us to register your attendance at the event, to assist with administrative purposes and for future planning and development of SeerPharma events and to allow compilation and analysis of statistics. The information provided in the online registration form and information provided at any time during an event, including without any limitation any feedback obtained during the event, will be used by SeerPharma to offer, provide and continue to improve its events and services, unless you indicate in writing that you do not want this information shared. SeerPharma will not otherwise, without your consent, disclose your personal information for any purpose unless it would reasonably be expected that such purpose is related to the provision and improvement of SeerPharma events or where such purpose is permitted or required by law.
Use of your personal information
The personal information which you provide to us will be used to provide products and services that you have requested or authorised. SeerPharma Pty Ltd may use the personal information to provide you with effective customer service and to improve the website.
Control of your personal information
Except as stated in this policy, the personal information you submit to will not be shared outside SeerPharma Pty Ltd and its associated companies without your permission.
You may elect to not receive further correspondence and have your details removed from SeerPharma’s mailing list by simply notifying SeerPharma. In the case of e-mail communications an automatic opt-out mechanism will be included for convenience.
How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?
Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information is never transmitted via email. SeerPharma may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.
For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, SeerPharma uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorised attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.
What Are Cookies?
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a Web site, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each Web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a Web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.
IP Addresses
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.
How We Use Cookies
Third party vendors, including Google, show our ads on sites on the internet. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.
Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page. Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative.
We use Cookies for the purposes of conducting Re-marketing Campaigns. Google’s Display Network use the DoubleClick Cookie. You can opt out of DoubleClick cookies by visiting the DoubleClick opt-out page or the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
A Special Note About Children
Children are not eligible to use our web site and services and we ask that minors (under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this site only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.
Changes to this statement
SeerPharma Pty Ltd may occasionally update this statement. When the statement is updated, we will indicate the date the statement was updated on the top of the privacy statement.
If changes to this privacy statement affect you, we will notify you either by placing a notice on the website or by sending you a notification directly.
SeerPharma Pty Ltd encourages you to periodically review this privacy statement so that you are informed as to how we protect your privacy. Your continued use of the services on our website constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.
Contact
If you have any questions regarding this Policy, or your dealings with our web site, please contact us.
